fifarenderz.com 2019-12-19

# Privacy Policy | FIFA Mobile 20 | FIFARenderZ

* * *

Please read this privacy policy carefully, it contains information on how this site uses your personal data. This document applies to all sites associated with fifarenderz.com and can change at any given time with notification. Changes made to this document will never give a user less privacy rights then in a previous version. 

### 1\. How does this site collect data?

This site itself only collects data when the user explicitly wants to share data, for example: an online form for a giveaway. This site does not collect or store any personal infomation on its own. See section 2 for third party data access. 

### 2\. Do third party applications have access to my data?

This site uses third party apps like Google Analytics and Google Adsense. Google Ads has its own policy, you can read up on it right here: 

  * <https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en>

You can opt-out of Google Adsense in your own Google account. This site or the owner is not responsible for Googles use of your personal data. 

### 3\. Can I request data deletion?

Yes. Every user has the right to delete their data. This includes everything that is saved on the site. If you would like to get in contact, you can send an email to 

_info@fifarenderz.com_

. The message must be written in English, you will not get a response if the message is written in any other language. The maximum response time is 7 business days. 

### 4\. Pollfish

This website uses Pollfish web plugin. Pollfish is an on-line survey platform, through which, anyone may conduct surveys. Pollfish collaborates with Developers of applications for smartphones and website owners in order to have access to users of such applications/websites and address survey questionnaires to them. This website uses and enables Pollfish cookies. When a user connects to this website, Pollfish detects whether the user is eligible for a survey. Data collected by Pollfish will be associated with your answers to the questionnaires whenever Pollfish sents such questionnaires to eligible users. For a full list of data received by Pollfish through this website, please read carefully Pollfish respondent terms located at https://www.pollfish.com/terms/respondent. By using this website you accept this privacy policy document and you hereby give your explicit consent for the placement of a Pollfish cookie in your system and the processing by Pollfish of the aforementioned data. Furthermore, you are informed that you may disable Pollfish operation at any time by using the Pollfish “opt out section” available on Pollfish website or by disabling “third party cookies” from your browser’s settings. We once more invite you to check the Pollfish respondent’s terms of use, if you wish to have more detailed view of the way Pollfish works works.   
APPLE, GOOGLE AND AMAZON ARE NOT A SPONSOR NOR ARE INVOLVED IN ANY WAY IN THIS CONTEST/DRAW. NO APPLE PRODUCTS ARE BEING USED AS PRIZES. 

### 5\. Any further information

You can contact the site's owner via email (

 _info@fifarenderz.com_

) for any further information. The message must be written in English, you will not get a response if the message is written in any other language. The maximum response time is 7 business days.
